UNITE Local 169 Files 6000/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Terrell's Potato Chips Co. (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Thermopatch (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Titan Power Inc. (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Tom Cat Bakery (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Tomra of North America Inc. (Box 10, Folder 53)
- The Top-flite Golf Company (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Tough Traveler (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Tower Records (MTS Corp.) (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Tracy Evans (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Trident Precision (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Tristate Industrial Laundries Inc. (Box 10, Folder 59)
- TUV TAAM CORP. (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Twin City Leather Corp. (Box 10, Folder 61)
- ULTREPET (Box 10, Folder 62)
- UNI Distribution (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Uniform by Park Coats (Box 11, Folder 2)
- United Cerebral Palsy - Albany Campaign (Box 11, Folder 3)
- U.S. Jazz Inc. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- United Industries Corp. (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Utrecht Manufacturing Corp. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Valentino Market (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Webster Plastics (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Winer Industries Inc. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Xerox Corp. (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Press Packet, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  April 17
- UNITE (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Local 169 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Labor - Internet (Box 11, Folder 14)
- LMRD (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Local Union Contacts (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Membership Statistics (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Recognition Aggreements (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Sunset Park (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Laundries (Box 11, Folder 20)
- "Desperation and Deception" (Box 11, Folder 21)
- UNITE (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Immigration Project (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Occupational Safety and Health Dept. (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Operations (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Organizing Dept. (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Political Dept. (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Research Dept. (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Central Labor Council (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Foundation Center (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Global Sweatshop Coalition (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Labor Religion Coalition (Box 11, Folder 32)
- National Labor Committee (Box 11, Folder 33)
- New Jersey Work Environment Council (Box 11, Folder 34)
- NYCOSH (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Sindicato Mexicano-Americano De Trabajadores (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Working Families Party (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Fulton County (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Family & Medical Leave Act (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Freedom of Information (Box 11, Folder 40)
  Letters and Information
- Sample Contracts (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Temporary Employees (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Lagos Campaign Material (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Lagos Campaign Material (Box 11, Folder 44)
- UNITE (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Child Labor Articles (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Steward Training - Anjerb Logo (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Mobilization (Box 12, Folder 1)
- John Sheilds (Box 12, Folder 2)
- New School Security Guards (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Re: Security Guards (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Re: Alex Tannor (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Security Guard Education (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Local 169 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- New School (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Scott Carter (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Security Records (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Security Guards - NSSR (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Security Guards - NSSR (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Unions - misc. (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Unions - Misc. (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Apex Leather Corp. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Carville National Leather Corp. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Colonial Training Corp. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Colonial Training Corp. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Joseph P. Conroy (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Fashion Training (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Fashion Tanning (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Fownes Brothers & Co. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- The Grandoe Corp. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- The Daniel Hayes Co. Inc. (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Johnstown Leather Corp. (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Kay's Caps Inc. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Milligans & Higgins (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Robinson & Smith Co. (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Sealy Mattresses (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Simco Leather Co. (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Swany American Corp. (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Tartan Textiles Services (Box 13, Folder 17)
- UltrePET LLC. (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Wood & Hyde Leather Co. (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Contracts: Armstrong Industrial Specialties, Inc., Greater Northern (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Contracts: Redmond Plastics Greater Northern (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Contracts: Schlegel Corp. Greater Northern (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Contracts: Service Machine Corp. Greater Northern (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Labor Day, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Petition Pearl Pant (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Park ULP's (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Request for Negotiation & Information (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Excelsior List (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Stipulation Election Agreement (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Meetings (Early) Pearl Paint (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Notes (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Negotiations (Canal SVA) (Box 13, Folder 32)
- ULP Pearl Paint (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Budget Pearl (Canal SVA) (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Letters to Pearl Paint (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Store Info (Box 13, Folder 36)
  Pearl Paint
- Contract Proposals (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Target Lists - Worker Lists Eligibility List (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Store Layout (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Company Memos - Pearl Paint (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Company Lit - Pearl Paint (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Federal Business Products Inc. / Federal Direct (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Pearl Paint (Paramus) (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Pearl (Woodbridge) (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Chicago (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Pearl Paint Employee Art Work (Box 13, Folder 46)
- KADA (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Old Cope (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Fast (Box 14, Folder 1)
- C-B Independent Union (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Independent Union of Chemical Workers (Box 14, Folder 3)
- League of International Federal Employees (Box 14, Folder 4)
- National Organization of Industrial Trade Union (NOITU) (Box 14, Folder 5)
- NOITU - Articles (Box 14, Folder 6)
- NYSNA Staff Union Professional Staff Coalition (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Organization of Union Representatives (OUR) (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Organization of Staff Analysts (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Security, Police, Fire Professionals of America (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Solidarity of Labor Organizations (SOLO) (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Union of Union Representatives (UUR) (Box 14, Folder 12)
- United Production Workers 17-18 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Dry Cleaning Industry (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Dry Cleaning Industry (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Jewelry Manufacturing Industry (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Jewelry Manufacturing Industry (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Laundry - Unite (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Mentally Retarded - Developmentally Disabled Industry (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Publishing Industry (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Taxi Drivers (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Waste Management Industry (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Taxi Drivers (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Waste Disposal Companies (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Waste Disposal Industry (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Gallery Systems (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Labor Arts (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Working New York - Photoshow (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Unite Lobbying Day (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Education Materials - Cornell University (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Education Materials - Cornell University (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Education Materials - Labor History (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Education Materials - Unite - Know Your Rights (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Member to Member Training (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Worker Education Center - Education Materials (Box 15, Folder 7)
- UNITE - Worker Education Programs (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Disability Benefits (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Duty of Fair Rep. (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Education Program Materials (Box 15, Folder 11)
- National Labor Relations Act - Text (Box 15, Folder 12)
- VDT Radiation (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Workplace Violence (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Workers Comp. (Box 15, Folder 15)
- UNITE (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Collective Bargaining Instruction Materials (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Collective Bargaining (Box 15, Folder 18)
- OSHA (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Safety and Health (Box 15, Folder 20)
- UNITE/OSHA (Box 15, Folder 21)
- UNITE/OSHA (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Steward Training Materials (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Steward Training Materials 2 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Weingarten Rights (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Local 169 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Pictures (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Rochester Bookstores (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Syracuse Area Bookstores (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Utica Area (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Queens Targets (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Buffalo/Rochester Area Colleges (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Albany Area Colleges (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Central New York (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Rochester Area Targets (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Syracuse Area NLRB Elections, 1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Rochester Area NLRB Elections, 1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Bread & Roses (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Tenants Neighbors (Box 16, Folder 14)
- NY State Newspapers (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Press Lists (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Nor'easters (Box 16, Folder 17)
- WTC - Local 169 Cards (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Membership Information (Box 16, Folder 19)
- NYC Area Retirees (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Logos (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Executive Council Meeting - Minutes - ANRJB (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Food Vendors - General (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Food Vendors - Articles (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Food Vendors Justice (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Food Vendors Dept. of Transportation (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Food Vendors - 5th Ave. BID (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Food Vendors - Dept. of Consumer Affairs (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Food Vendors - Grand Central Partnership (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Street Vendor Project/Sean Basinski (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Food Vendors - Proposed Legislation - Parks Dept. (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Local 19V Charter Info (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Parcel to Mr. Mike Donovan (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Vendors Correspondence - Public Advocate (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Local 169 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Food Vendors - General Information (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Food Vendors - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Food Vendors - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Vendors - HIQA (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Vendors Correspondence - Public Advocate Office (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Mobile food Vendors - IRS Rules for Calculating Taxes (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Local 169V - Press Releases (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Midtown Pretzel Depot Closure (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Food Vendors - George Karantzias (See also GKPS) (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Food Vendors - Department of Health (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Intro #160 - Vendors (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Katehis, Anastasio Permit Revocation (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Tressie Smiley - Food Vendors (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Emmanuel Tsambouniers - Food Vendors (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Food Vendors - rules & Regulations - Health Dept. (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Food Vendors Rules and Regulations - Parks Dept. (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Food Vendors - Kyriakos Maroulleits (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Food Vendors - Disabled Veterans Law (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Food Vendors - Intro No. 468 - Illegal Vendors (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Paul Schubert - Vendors (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Dept. of Health Proposed Regulation Changes (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Konstantino (GUS) Agyros (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Konstantino (GUS) Agyros (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Vendors - Department of Sanitation (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Street Vendor Project (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Vendors: Greek Stuff (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Vendors Propane Tanks (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Vendors - Artists (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Vendor Proposals (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Vendors Dan Rossi (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Vendors - Dan Rossi (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Vendors - A to Z Kosher Meats (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Vendors - Press Releases (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Permits & Licenses (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Food Vendors - Jose Cagua (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Food Vendors - Mohamed El Hoummad (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Chowdhury, Mohammed Kamrul - Permit Revocation (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Food Vendors - Mohammed Farid (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Georgis Karagiannis - License Revocation (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Mohammed Y. Khan (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Katehis, Vasilios Permit Revocation (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Food Vendors - Jimmy Hom (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Kasimis, Aristocrats Permit Revocation (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Vendors - Sophie Laskaris (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Food Vendors - Gus Terezis - Bank Leumi Problem (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Food Vendors - ID Cards (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Notes I (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Notes II (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Notes III (Box 17, Folder 39)
- At-A-Glance, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- At-A-Glance, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 41)